https://www.xfab.com/privacy-statement/

My X-FAB LoginContactCareerInvestorsSearch
About X-FABCorporate OverviewKey FactsLocationsOur ValuesQualityQuality ManagementQualification & ReliabilityProcess QualificationWLRYield ManagementFailure AnalysisFailure Analysis Tool SetCertificatesRoHS & REACHEHS PolicyCareerNewsSeasons Greetings 2020InvestorsInvestor NewsFinancial ReportsFinancial CalendarX-FAB ShareShareholder StructureShareholders MeetingAnalyst CoverageTransparency NotificationsCorporate GovernanceBoard of DirectorsEventsWebinar OverviewMore than MooreWhat is More than Moore?Analog Design EcosystemMarketsAutomotiveMedicalIndustrialCommunication & ConsumerApplicationsOptoAPD & SPAD SensorsAmbient Light SensorPDICHigh VoltageAC LED Lighting ControllerBLDC Motor ControllerPrecision AnalogSignal Conditioning ICAutomotiveSolenoid DriverTechnologyTechnology OverviewCMOS0.18 µm - XH0180.18 µm - XC0180.18 µm - XP0180.18 µm - XS0180.25 µm - 0.25 FC0.35 µm - XH0350.35 µm - XA0350.35 µm - XO0350.35 µm - XU0350.6 µm - XC060.6 µm - XB060.6 µm - XHB060.8 µm - CX081.0 µm - XC10Galvanic IsolationSOI0.18 µm - XT0180.6 µm - XT061.0 µm - XI101.0 µm - XDH101.0 µm - XDM10SiCNVMApplication SpaceNVM Memory PrinciplesTesting ConceptEasyZapEasyFuseNV LatchesTrimOTPMTP/CEEPROMEEPROMNVRAMOTPFlashRFMEMSMEMS Foundry ServiceManufacturingQualityProcess CapabilitiesDesign SupportVirtual wafer processingDesign and Optimization of KOH Etch MasksFinite Elements SimulationCollaborationSilicon-based MicrofluidicsMEMS Sensors & ActuatorsCustomer Specific ProcessesOpen Platform ProcessesRelative Pressure SensorsAbsolute Pressure SensorsInfrared SensorsInertial SensorsIntegrated CMOS/MEMSServiceService OfferingFeatureXplorerResourceXplorerDesign SupportEDA PartnersMy X-FAB | Customer PortalHotline ServiceAnalog IPESD SupportDigital IPPrototyping SupportMPW ScheduleMLM ServiceManufacturing SupportProcess LongevitySupply Chain ManagementThird Party ServicesIP PortalX-CHAINOutsourcingOutsourcing ScenariosEngagement ModelsCapabilities
Datenschutzerklärung (German version)
Privacy StatementX-FAB Silicon Foundries SE (hereafter "X-FAB") takes its responsibility to protect your personal data very seriously and strictly observes the applicable European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). This website collects personal data only to the extent that is required for technical reasons. The data we collect is never sold or passed on to third parties. This statement presents an overview of the methods we use to guarantee this protection and specifies the kind of data collected for each particular purpose.
Data processing on this website
When you access our website, your web browser automatically provides data to our web server for technical reasons. This data will include items such as time and date of access, URL of the referring web page, file accessed, volume of data sent, name and version of your browser, your operating system and your IP address. These items of data are stored separately from other data that you enter while making use of our web presence. It is impossible for us to associate these data items with a particular individual. These items of data are evaluated for statistical purposes and then deleted.
Cookies
To enhance the functionality and usability of our web presence, we make use of so-called "cookies." These cookies can be used to store items of data on your computer when you access our website. You have the option of preventing the storage of cookies on your computer by making appropriate changes to your browser settings. However, if you do so, you may reduce the range of functionalities offered by our website. Cookies are not harmful to your computer and contain no viruses.
Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”).  It is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Please note the following: In the USA, the European Union considers that there is no “adequate level of protection” for the processing of personal data in accordance with EU standards. However, this level of protection can be replaced for individual companies by certification according to the so-called “EU-U.S. Privacy Shield”. Google is certified according to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield. Google Analytics cookies are stored based on Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage.  Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.  You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.  By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
As your privacy is important to us we are using the function "_anonymizeIp()" as part of the Google Analytics service. This function makes sure that only abbreviated IP addresses are processed to rule out that a direct reference to a person can be made. You may withdraw your consent to the collection and storage of your data in the future at anytime. By activating the below checkbox the tracking of your activities on this website is disabled completely. To disable the tracking permanently your browser has to accept cookies. Please notice that deleting the browser cache may result in losing those cookies and thus the setting of tracking disablement.
Alternatively, you may prevent data collection through the installation of a Google browser plug-in. This plug-in will block the usage of Google Analytics for all websites you may visit.
Check this box to disable Google Analytics for this website
Links to other websites
This website contains external links to third-party websites whose content is not under our control. Accordingly, we cannot offer any guarantees for this third-party content. The respective provider or operator of the pages linked has sole responsibility for the content of these pages.
Plugins and tools
YouTube Our website uses plugins from YouTube, which is operated by Google. The operator of the pages is YouTube LLC, 901 Cherry Ave., San Bruno, CA 94066, USA. If you visit one of our pages featuring a YouTube plugin, a connection to the YouTube servers is established. Here the YouTube server is informed about which of our pages you have visited. YouTube is used to help make our website appealing. This constitutes a justified interest pursuant to Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR. If you're logged in to your YouTube account, YouTube allows you to associate your browsing behavior directly with your personal profile. You can prevent this by logging out of your YouTube account. Further information about handling user data, can be found in the data protection declaration of YouTube under https://policies.google.com/privacy.
Right to obtain information
At any time, you have the right to request details of the data we store about you, its origin and recipient, and the purpose for which it is stored. Details of stored data are provided by the Data Protection Officer. You also have the right to request that it be corrected, blocked, or deleted. You can contact us by sending an e-mail to bsdb@xfab.com  if you have further questions about the issue of privacy and data protection.  If you believe that the processing of your personal data violates legal requirements, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a competent data protection supervisory authority (Art. 77 GDPR).
Security
We use technical and organizational security measures to protect your data managed by us against manipulation, loss, destruction and against access by unauthorized persons. We are constantly improving our security measures in line with technological developments.
Further information
We value your trust. Therefore we are willing to share with you all information you may require in regards to the handling of your personal data. If you have any questions not answered by this Privacy Statement or need more detailed information on a particular topic, then please do not hesitate to contact the X-FAB Data Protection Officer.
About X-FABCorporate OverviewQualityCareerNewsInvestorsEventsMore than MooreMarketsAutomotiveMedicalIndustrialCommunication & ConsumerApplicationsTechnologyTechnology OverviewCMOSSOISiCNVMRFMEMSMEMS Foundry ServiceSilicon-based MicrofluidicsMEMS Sensors & ActuatorsServiceService OfferingFeatureXplorerResourceXplorerDesign SupportPrototyping SupportManufacturing SupportThird Party ServicesOutsourcing
Available on the AppStore
Android App on Google Play
Facebook
Twitter
Linkedin
goto Top
My X-FAB LoginDownload CenterInvestors
SearchSitemapImprintPrivacy Statement© X-FAB Silicon Foundries SE 2020
